let quiz_questions = [
    // question 1
    {
        // question
        question: "3 x 2 = ?",

        // options
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "4 x 5 = ?",

        options: ["15", "18", "20", "25"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 3,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "6 x 3 = ?",

        options: ["12", "15", "18", "21"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 3,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "2 x 8 = ?",

        options: ["10", "12", "14", "16"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 4,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "5 x 7 = ?",

        options: ["30", "35", "40", "45"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 2,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "9 x 4 = ?",

        options: ["27", "32", "36", "40"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 3,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "8 x 2 = ?",

        options: ["10", "14", "16", "20"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 3,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },
    {
        // write yout question here
        question: "3 x 9 = ?",

        options: ["24", "25", "26", "27"],
        // correct option (1,2,3,4 etc)
        answer: 4,
        //    selected_answer:null
    },

    // question 9 starts

    // question 1
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the value of the digit 4 in the number 435?",

        // options
        options: ["4", "40", "400", "None of the above"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 3,
    },

    // question 2
    {
        // question
        question:
            "Which is the largest number in the following list: 12, 22, 32, 42?",

        // options
        options: ["12", "22", "32", "42"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 4,
    },

    // question 3
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the sum of 6 and 9?",

        // options
        options: ["12", "15", "18", "21"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 4
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the difference between 25 and 11?",

        // options
        options: ["11", "14", "16", "None of the above"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 5
    {
        // question
        question: "Which of the following is an odd number?",

        // options
        options: ["14", "17", "22", "28"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 6
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the product of 4 and 5?",

        // options
        options: ["9", "16", "20", "None of the above"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 3,
    },

    // question 7
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the next number in the pattern: 2, 4, 6, 8, __?",

        // options
        options: ["10", "12", "14", "16"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 1,
    },

    // question 8
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the largest 2-digit number?",

        // options
        options: ["89", "99", "109", "119"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 9
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the quotient of 18 divided by 3?",

        // options
        options: ["3", "6", "9", "12"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 10
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the value of the digit 5 in the number 257?",

        // options
        options: ["5", "50", "500", "None of the above"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 2,
    },

    // question 19
    {
        // question
        question: "What is the value of the digit '3' in the number 423?",

        // options
        options: ["3", "30", "300", "3,000"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 1, // The value of the digit '3' in the number 423 is in the ones place, which has a place value of 1. Therefore, the value of the digit '3' is 3 x 1
    },

    // question 20
    {
        // question
        question:
            "If a rectangle has a length of 5 units and a width of 3 units, what is its perimeter?",

        // options
        options: ["8 units", "10 units", "13 units", "16 units"],

        // correct answer
        answer: 4, // The perimeter of a rectangle is found by adding up the lengths of all its sides. In this case, the length is 5 units and the width is 3 units, so the perimeter is 2 x (5 units + 3 units) = 2 x 8 units = 16 units.
    },
];
